<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dropped Bits</title>
    <link>https://droppedbits.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dropped Bits</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 17:45:40 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://droppedbits.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>December 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2022/01/15/december-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 17:45:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2022/01/15/december-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to another edition of Dispatches from Dropped Bits HQ! I hope your holidays were as good as they could be, given All This™.
This month, on top of a quick recap of 2021, I want to talk a bit about where I see Dropped Bits going in 2022. January marks the company&amp;rsquo;s ten-year anniversary — something that kinda snuck up on me, if I&amp;rsquo;m honest. I&amp;rsquo;d imagined some kind of fanfare, along with a whole new webpage to mark the occasion, and that… didn&amp;rsquo;t happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/12/15/november-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/12/15/november-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re nearly at the end of the year, and it&amp;rsquo;s certainly been an interesting one.
My goal for 2021 was to get Dropped Bits to break even, after losing money for years, and I&amp;rsquo;ve done that. I launched a new app, Thought Detox, for the first time in six years. While it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been a runaway success, it has brought in enough money to cover base expenses. I sunsetted my first app, HoneyJar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/11/15/october-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/11/15/october-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the 15th of November, and you know what that means — a monthly update on how things are going at Dropped Bits HQ!
October is always an interesting month, at least here in Montreal. The city feels like it&amp;rsquo;s got one foot in summer, and the other in winter; there&amp;rsquo;s a sort-of-refusal to accept that the heat and daylight we&amp;rsquo;ve been enjoying since late May is winding down, and at the same time some excitement kicking off preparation for the first snow and the holidays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/10/15/september-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 16:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/10/15/september-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>Hello, friends!
If you’ve been reading these regularly, you might have noticed that there was no first-Wednesday-of-the-month post last week, nor was there a mid-month update in September. There are two reasons for that.
First, there hasn&amp;rsquo;t been much to report. September was pretty quiet, aside from releasing a very early, mostly-incomplete version of Per&amp;rsquo;s redesign to internal testers.
Second, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided it makes sense to send out just one update a month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/09/01/august-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 07:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/09/01/august-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re a few days into a &amp;ldquo;back-to-school&amp;rdquo; sale on Per (USD $0.99 instead of USD $2.99), with a new release that includes translation to French being around the corner.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the download numbers looked like for August:
Per: 3 downloads (-57% ▽) Thought Detox: 5 downloads (+67% △) Revenues and proceeds on June sales are estimates based on the information I get from Apple, in US Dollars.
Revenues, August 2021: USD$7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indie Tools: Wave Accounting</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/08/18/indie-tools-wave-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 07:27:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/08/18/indie-tools-wave-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Indie Tools is a series that dives into the apps and services I use to run my bootstrapped indie-development business. These work for me, but may not be right for you.
My first career was accounting and small-business consulting, which has been helpful in running my own business. I&amp;rsquo;m really comfortable with the idea of profit-and-loss reports, balance sheets, and cash flow, and so I haven&amp;rsquo;t had much of a need for accounting and bookkeeping services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/08/04/july-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 07:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/08/04/july-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>July continued to be a quiet month for sales, so I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to think a little bit bigger with the business and have moved some contracting work in. There are a few advantages to doing this for my particular situation, but as far as my goal of making the business profitable this year, it feels like a bit of a cheat — the goal was to make the app business profitable, and so I&amp;rsquo;m going to continue to focus on that part here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates! Updates! Updates!</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/07/21/updates-updates-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 06:30:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/07/21/updates-updates-updates/</guid>
      <description>My Updates I wanted to share a couple of updates on Thought Detox here.
First, a French translation of the app is now being beta tested. I&amp;rsquo;ve done the translation myself; my French isn&amp;rsquo;t bad, thanks to immersion programs in high school. Still, it&amp;rsquo;s far from perfect, so if you see something that&amp;rsquo;s off, please let me know.
The French language often uses significantly more words than English to express the same thing, so sometimes that affects UI elements — for example, the &amp;ldquo;Release Another&amp;rdquo; button ends up being titled « Libérer une autre pensée » in French.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/07/06/june-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 10:04:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/07/06/june-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>Financially, June is always a down month for cash flow due to income taxes. More specifically, while there aren&amp;rsquo;t usually any taxes to pay (because the company has been operating at a loss for the last little while), the filing fees I pay to submit the tax returns has eaten up a major chunk of the cash inflows so far in 2021.
Anyways, here’s what the download numbers looked like for June:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Short Update</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/06/16/a-short-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 06:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/06/16/a-short-update/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re nearly halfway through the year, and Apple&amp;rsquo;s World Wide Developer Conference (WWDC, or &amp;ldquo;Dub Dub&amp;rdquo; for those in the know) has come and gone. It&amp;rsquo;s a special time of year for iOS and Mac developers, where new features of the platform are announced, along with ways to build for them. There&amp;rsquo;s always more there than I can consume during the week that the conference runs, but I&amp;rsquo;m slowly catching up, and I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to see what&amp;rsquo;s coming to iOS 15 and macOS 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/06/02/may-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 06:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/06/02/may-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>Recap: May 2021 Looking purely at dollars, May appears to continue the downward trend of sales for Thought Detox. However, because the app was on sale all month, downloads are actually up. And, again, this is a very small number of downloads, big percentage changes might still be in the margin of error for number of units.
Here’s what the download numbers looked like for April:
Per: 5 downloads (-17% ▽) Thought Detox: 7 downloads (+40% △) Revenues and proceeds on May sales are estimates based on the information I get from Apple, in US Dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Do You Detox?</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/05/19/how-do-you-detox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 06:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/05/19/how-do-you-detox/</guid>
      <description>When I created the original Thought Detox web app, it was meant to be a digital version of a traditionally-analogue concept: take a thought that&amp;rsquo;s upsetting to you, write about it on a piece of paper, and then throw away that piece of paper. And there&amp;rsquo;s evidence that this works, too:
As it happens, writing down your negative thoughts on a piece of paper and then physically throwing this piece of paper in the trash lessens the salience of these thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/05/05/april-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 07:15:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/05/05/april-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>Recap: April 2021 April appears to continue the downward trend of sales for Thought Detox, though frankly in this very small range of downloads, big percentage changes might still be in the margin of error for number of units.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the download numbers looked like for April:
Per: 6 downloads (+100% △) Thought Detox: 5 downloads (-50% ▽) Revenues and proceeds on April sales are estimates based on the information I get form Apple, in US Dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking About Syncing</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/04/21/thinking-about-syncing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/04/21/thinking-about-syncing/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m working towards the next major feature of Thought Detox: making it available on the iPad and the Mac.
Well, sort of. That&amp;rsquo;s more of the end goal for the actual next feature that I&amp;rsquo;m working on: adding another way for you to track your time writing in the app.
Persistence Right now, if you choose to track your writing time, the app does so by storing it as Mindful Minutes in the Health app on your iPhone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/04/07/march-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 07:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/04/07/march-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>Recap: March 2021 Compared to February, with the new app launch, March has been much slower. While that&amp;rsquo;s pretty much what I expected, I didn&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;d be this much slower. That&amp;rsquo;s okay! It gives me a baseline to compare against as I try things.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the download numbers looked like for March:
Per: 3 downloads (-63% ▽) Thought Detox: 10 downloads (-92% ▽) Revenues and proceeds on March sales are estimates based on the information I get from Apple, in US Dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kind Business</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/03/17/kind-of-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 07:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/03/17/kind-of-business/</guid>
      <description>Growing up watching my parents run a small family business made some lasting impressions on me.
First and foremost: the importance of taking care of your customers. They didn&amp;rsquo;t charge a whole lot for their services, but bent over backwards to serve their customers, often working weekends, and rarely taking a vacation. While I don&amp;rsquo;t think that&amp;rsquo;s especially healthy, that focus on customer service stuck with me, and evolved into a strong user advocacy in any products I&amp;rsquo;m involved with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thought Detox: Updates and Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/03/10/thought-detox-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 07:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/03/10/thought-detox-update/</guid>
      <description>Thought Detox v2021.02 Released Happy Wednesday, friends! A small update has been released and includes the following changes:
The Settings button is now hidden during the release animation, to match the Release button. Fixed a bug that affected VoiceOver users reading through the bar graph, where the day wasn&amp;rsquo;t always read out correctly. Made changes under the hood to better sync the graph between the app and the widget. You can check which version of the app you&amp;rsquo;re running by opening the Settings sheet and scrolling to the bottom of the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/03/03/february-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 06:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/03/03/february-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>Recap: February 2021 Just like last month, most of my time was spent working on launching Thought Detox on the App Store. This had a lot more to do with all of the other moving parts, besides the app: the landing page, the marketing copy, the press emails, and the Product Hunt announcement.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the download numbers looked like for February:
HoneyJar: 9 downloads (-55% ▽) Per: 8 downloads (+14% △) Thought Detox: 127 downloads Thought Detox is the only paid app; it was available for pre-order at USD$0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thought Detox Launch: A Retrospective</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/24/thought-detox-launch-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/24/thought-detox-launch-update/</guid>
      <description>Thought Detox has now been available for sale on the App Store since February 15th, with pre-orders opening one week before that. I&amp;rsquo;m going to focus the discussion on the following timeframes:
8-14 February (pre-order week) 15-21 February (launch week) Prior to that, I was sharing some of my work on the app via my personal Twitter account, and set up a beta-testing program via AppAirport. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get a whole lot of feedback from public beta testing, but it was useful to check that the app wasn&amp;rsquo;t crashing anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thought Detox Launch Sale Extended 🚀</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/17/thought-detox-launch-sale-extended/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/17/thought-detox-launch-sale-extended/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s official! Thought Detox is available for sale on the App Store, and to celebrate, I&amp;rsquo;m extending the sale price.
The official website also went live Sunday night. Many thanks to Christina Szilbereisz for her work on the design — I&amp;rsquo;m really thrilled with how it turned out!
I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen a tonne of downloads yet, but nonetheless, Thought Detox has done way better on launch than other apps I&amp;rsquo;ve released, which I&amp;rsquo;m really thrilled about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thought Detox Pre-Launch Sale!</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/10/thought-detox-presale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/10/thought-detox-presale/</guid>
      <description>Thought Detox is available for pre-order!
The app launches on the App Store on Monday, February 15th, but readers can pre-order it today at 65% off the launch price.
Yes — Thought Detox will be a paid app. I don&amp;rsquo;t think anyone believes that people shouldn&amp;rsquo;t get paid for their work, but some business models are harder to accept than others.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s agree straight away that supporting the app with advertising isn&amp;rsquo;t a good fit here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/03/updates-january-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 05:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/03/updates-january-2021/</guid>
      <description>In the interest of transparency, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided that the first update of every month should include a recap of how things went the month before. Let me know if you find this useful!
Recap: January 2021 Most of my time was spent working on the Thought Detox launch (more on this below). I&amp;rsquo;ve been telling myself that &amp;ldquo;release is imminent&amp;rdquo; for a couple of months now, but there&amp;rsquo;s always something more to do!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Last updated 11 February, 2024
Our approach to privacy is pretty straightforward—we avoid collecting private information if we don&amp;rsquo;t have to, and if we do, we respect and protect it.
It&amp;rsquo;s important, however, to consider the difference between private and anonymous data.
Anonymous data Analytics We&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to use Plausible Analytics to track usage of websites (including droppedbits.com) because it does a great job of providing useful data without, in their own words, &amp;ldquo;collecting any personal data or personally identifiable information (PII), without using cookies and while respecting the privacy of [our] website visitors&amp;rdquo; — this means that you&amp;rsquo;re not tracked across devices, websites, and apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Whole New App</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/01/27/a-whole-new-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/01/27/a-whole-new-app/</guid>
      <description>You may have seen this tweet yesterday:
This content is no longer available.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been teasing the work I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing on the first new Dropped Bits app since… wow, 2015? Has it been that long since I launched Per?
Thought Detox for iPhone It&amp;rsquo;s coming, and it&amp;rsquo;s based on this Glitch app that I built in vanilla HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to tell you all more about it soon, but for now if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in testing the public beta, it&amp;rsquo;s available on Airport (here&amp;rsquo;s a direct link).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy Update</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/01/16/privacy-policy-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/01/16/privacy-policy-update/</guid>
      <description>In 2019&amp;rsquo;s site update, analytics were ripped out while I looked for a more privacy-focused option. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce that the site now uses privacy-respecting Plausible Analytics, and I&amp;rsquo;ve updated the privacy policy to reflect this.
Plausible Analytics is an open-source project dedicated to making web analytics more privacy-friendly. Our mission is to reduce corporate surveillance by providing an alternative web analytics tool which doesn’t come from the AdTech world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death by a Thousand Cuts</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2019/06/25/death-by-a-thousand-cuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2019/06/25/death-by-a-thousand-cuts/</guid>
      <description>Lately, there’s been a lot of handwringing about the long-term impact of a daily treat like a cup of coffee. The Times got this completely wrong yesterday, pushing people deeper into a trap that they should run away from. And the Washington Post points out that the number of people getting a loan for their wedding is skyrocketing. This is a problem.
— Source: The tyranny of small debts, compounded (Seth Godin)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;ve been renovating.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2019/05/31/weve-been-renovating/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2019/05/31/weve-been-renovating/</guid>
      <description>After a (much longer than expected) hiatus from posting here, the site is back with a fresh new design!
There hasn&amp;rsquo;t been very much going on for a while, but that&amp;rsquo;s changing. Dropped Bits is a one-person shop, and the bulk of my time has been taken up by Other Things™ for some time now. I&amp;rsquo;ve since managed to cull lots of those projects, so that I can dedicate more time here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get in touch</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>Have a comment or question? Need support? Want to know more?
Send me an email, and I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to get back to you within one business day. Remember, your e-mail address will never be used for anything but answering your question.
If you prefer, you can also reach out via Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HoneyJar</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/apps/honeyjar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/apps/honeyjar/</guid>
      <description>While no longer available for sale, HoneyJar was a future-value calculator inspired by one of Aesop&amp;rsquo;s fables:
A jar of honey was upset and the sticky sweetness flowed out on the table. The sweet smell of the honey soon brought a large number of Flies buzzing around. They did not wait for an invitation. No, indeed; they settled right down, feet and all, to gorge themselves. The Flies were quickly smeared from head to foot with honey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Per</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/apps/per/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/apps/per/</guid>
      <description>Per helps you shop smarter by figuring out what gets you more for your money.
At its heart, Per is a price-per-unit calculator. Just give it the price and quantity for two options, tap the Compare button, and let Per figure out which one gives you the best deal.
Of course, you can do that kind of math with a basic calculator app. Per brings a few neat little tricks to the comparison-shopping party, though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free non-trial for apps</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/02/free-non-trial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/02/free-non-trial/</guid>
      <description>On Friday, both Per and HoneyJar were made free for a limited time.
We don&#39;t really need Per to tell us which option is the better deal. Developers can&amp;rsquo;t offer free trials to their customers on the App Store, and customers aren&amp;rsquo;t always willing to commit dollars to new apps. That&amp;rsquo;s normal. Even though most apps cost less than a cup of coffee, at least a cup of coffee is something that people know and understand—everyone knows what a cup of coffee offers and can easily decide if it&amp;rsquo;s worth the price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now saving you even more money!</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/01/now-saving-you-even-more-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/01/now-saving-you-even-more-money/</guid>
      <description>How do you make two money-saving apps even better for your bottom line? Easy! Per and HoneyJar are both free for a limited time!
Download them now on the App Store and watch your savings add up even faster!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Per v1.1 released</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/23/per-v11-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/23/per-v11-released/</guid>
      <description>A few little tweaks, enhancements, and bug fixes for you in this new version of Per:
See all the things Some view adjustments for iPhone 4s and iPhone 5/5c/5s users now put all the fields on screen, for more happy-tappy UI goodness.
Globalization, yo You can now choose the type of non-metric units used in your area (US vs. UK) from the Info page.
Nuke the site from orbit (it&amp;rsquo;s the only way to be sure) You can now clear the text from all the fields with one button tap, from the new Clear button (⊗) in the keyboard toolbar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the App Store, developers can&#39;t hear you scream.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/16/developers-cant-hear-you-scream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/16/developers-cant-hear-you-scream/</guid>
      <description>A note if you&amp;rsquo;re leaving a review for any app on the App Store:
Reviews are very helpful for letting the world know what you think of an app. Additionally, the more reviews an app gets, the higher it ranks when someone searches the App Store, which improves its visibility and &amp;ldquo;discoverability&amp;rdquo;. Developers of the app can&amp;rsquo;t reply to your reviews. So, if your review contains some kind of support request (&amp;ldquo;the app crashes when I do X&amp;rdquo;), the developer can&amp;rsquo;t get in touch with you to help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, Per.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/09/hello-per/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/09/hello-per/</guid>
      <description>Pop quiz, hotshot: you&amp;rsquo;re in produce section at the supermarket, and you need carrots for tonight&amp;rsquo;s dinner.
Raw carrots are $1.09 per pound. Washed baby carrots are $1.99 for 907 grams.
What do you do?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
Per was created to answer exactly that question. It was inspired by my wife, who literally turned to me at the grocery store and said,
&amp;ldquo;You should write an app that tells me which of these options is a better deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honeyjar v1.1 released</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/10/09/honeyjar-v11-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/10/09/honeyjar-v11-released/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve just released v1.1 of HoneyJar, a free update now available on the App Store.
This version adds support for iOS 8 and fixes a display bug on the iPhones 6, along with a smattering of other small bug fixes and performance enhancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, HoneyJar.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/09/04/hello-honeyjar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/09/04/hello-honeyjar/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to announce that HoneyJar, our first app for iPhone and iPod touch, has been released for sale.
You give every dollar you spend a job, whether you realize it or not.
In fact—if you want to take it to the extreme—you can argue that every dollar that isn&amp;rsquo;t working for you, is working against you. It&amp;rsquo;s keeping you from an early retirement. It&amp;rsquo;s keeping you from financial independence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/08/25/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/08/25/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to announce that—after what feels like an eternity—our first app for iPhone, HoneyJar, was submitted on Sunday for approval to the App Store team.
This marks a pretty big milestone, obviously. Dropped Bits incorporated almost three years ago, so it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time coming, too. And it&amp;rsquo;s been an interesting road so far, full of inspiration, hard decisions, learning, sacrifice, and happy little victories.
Turns out, going from idea to shipping your Minimum Viable Product isn&amp;rsquo;t as simple as you&amp;rsquo;d think—especially when your organization is having an identity crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
