<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Dropped Bits</title>
    <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Dropped Bits</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 06:30:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://droppedbits.com/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>February 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/03/03/february-2021-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 06:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/03/03/february-2021-updates/</guid>
      <description>Recap: February 2021 Just like last month, most of my time was spent working on launching Thought Detox on the App Store. This had a lot more to do with all of the other moving parts, besides the app: the landing page, the marketing copy, the press emails, and the Product Hunt announcement.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the download numbers looked like for February:
 HoneyJar: 9 downloads (-55% ▽) Per: 8 downloads (+14% △) Thought Detox: 127 downloads  Thought Detox is the only paid app; it was available for pre-order at USD$0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thought Detox Launch: A Retrospective</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/24/thought-detox-launch-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/24/thought-detox-launch-update/</guid>
      <description>Thought Detox has now been available for sale on the App Store since February 15th, with pre-orders opening one week before that. I&amp;rsquo;m going to focus the discussion on the following timeframes:
 8-14 February (pre-order week) 15-21 February (launch week)  Prior to that, I was sharing some of my work on the app via my personal Twitter account, and set up a beta-testing program via AppAirport. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get a whole lot of feedback from public beta testing, but it was useful to check that the app wasn&amp;rsquo;t crashing anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thought Detox Launch Sale Extended 🚀</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/17/thought-detox-launch-sale-extended/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/17/thought-detox-launch-sale-extended/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s official! Thought Detox is available for sale on the App Store, and to celebrate, I&amp;rsquo;m extending the sale price.
The official website also went live Sunday night. Many thanks to Christina Szilbereisz for her work on the design — I&amp;rsquo;m really thrilled with how it turned out!
I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen a tonne of downloads yet, but nonetheless, Thought Detox has done way better on launch than other apps I&amp;rsquo;ve released, which I&amp;rsquo;m really thrilled about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thought Detox Pre-Launch Sale!</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/10/thought-detox-presale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/10/thought-detox-presale/</guid>
      <description>Thought Detox is available for pre-order!
The app launches on the App Store on Monday, February 15th, but readers can pre-order it today at 65% off the launch price.
 Yes — Thought Detox will be a paid app. I don&amp;rsquo;t think anyone believes that people shouldn&amp;rsquo;t get paid for their work, but some business models are harder to accept than others.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s agree straight away that supporting the app with advertising isn&amp;rsquo;t a good fit here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2021 Updates</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/03/updates-january-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 05:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/02/03/updates-january-2021/</guid>
      <description>In the interest of transparency, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided that the first update of every month should include a recap of how things went the month before. Let me know if you find this useful!
Recap: January 2021 Most of my time was spent working on the Thought Detox launch (more on this below). I&amp;rsquo;ve been telling myself that &amp;ldquo;release is imminent&amp;rdquo; for a couple of months now, but there&amp;rsquo;s always something more to do!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Whole New App</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/01/27/a-whole-new-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/01/27/a-whole-new-app/</guid>
      <description>You may have seen this tweet yesterday:
Thought Detox is now publicly available for beta testing! Check it out via @AppAirport: https://t.co/S0Nj4lpdUT pic.twitter.com/IDpWKv3BnL
&amp;mdash; Dropped Bits (@DroppedBitsHQ) January 26, 2021  I&amp;rsquo;ve been teasing the work I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing on the first new Dropped Bits app since… wow, 2015? Has it been that long since I launched Per?
Thought Detox for iPhone It&amp;rsquo;s coming, and it&amp;rsquo;s based on this Glitch app that I built in vanilla HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy Update</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/01/16/privacy-policy-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2021/01/16/privacy-policy-update/</guid>
      <description>In 2019&amp;rsquo;s site update, analytics were ripped out while I looked for a more privacy-focused option. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce that the site now uses privacy-respecting Plausible Analytics, and I&amp;rsquo;ve updated the privacy policy to reflect this.
 Plausible Analytics is an open-source project dedicated to making web analytics more privacy-friendly. Our mission is to reduce corporate surveillance by providing an alternative web analytics tool which doesn’t come from the AdTech world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death by a Thousand Cuts</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2019/06/25/death-by-a-thousand-cuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2019/06/25/death-by-a-thousand-cuts/</guid>
      <description>Lately, there’s been a lot of handwringing about the long-term impact of a daily treat like a cup of coffee. The Times got this completely wrong yesterday, pushing people deeper into a trap that they should run away from. And the Washington Post points out that the number of people getting a loan for their wedding is skyrocketing. This is a problem.
 — Source: The tyranny of small debts, compounded (Seth Godin)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;ve been renovating.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2019/05/31/weve-been-renovating/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2019/05/31/weve-been-renovating/</guid>
      <description>After a (much longer than expected) hiatus from posting here, the site is back with a fresh new design!
There hasn&amp;rsquo;t been very much going on for a while, but that&amp;rsquo;s changing. Dropped Bits is a one-person shop, and the bulk of my time has been taken up by Other Things™ for some time now. I&amp;rsquo;ve since managed to cull lots of those projects, so that I can dedicate more time here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free non-trial for apps</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/02/free-non-trial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/02/free-non-trial/</guid>
      <description>On Friday, both Per and HoneyJar were made free for a limited time.
 We don&#39;t really need Per to tell us which option is the better deal.  Developers can&amp;rsquo;t offer free trials to their customers on the App Store, and customers aren&amp;rsquo;t always willing to commit dollars to new apps. That&amp;rsquo;s normal. Even though most apps cost less than a cup of coffee, at least a cup of coffee is something that people know and understand—everyone knows what a cup of coffee offers and can easily decide if it&amp;rsquo;s worth the price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now saving you even more money!</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/01/now-saving-you-even-more-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/05/01/now-saving-you-even-more-money/</guid>
      <description>How do you make two money-saving apps even better for your bottom line? Easy! Per and HoneyJar are both free for a limited time!
Download them now on the App Store and watch your savings add up even faster!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Per v1.1 released</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/23/per-v11-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/23/per-v11-released/</guid>
      <description>A few little tweaks, enhancements, and bug fixes for you in this new version of Per:
See all the things Some view adjustments for iPhone 4s and iPhone 5/5c/5s users now put all the fields on screen, for more happy-tappy UI goodness.
Globalization, yo You can now choose the type of non-metric units used in your area (US vs. UK) from the Info page.
Nuke the site from orbit (it&amp;rsquo;s the only way to be sure) You can now clear the text from all the fields with one button tap, from the new Clear button (⊗) in the keyboard toolbar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the App Store, developers can&#39;t hear you scream.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/16/developers-cant-hear-you-scream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/16/developers-cant-hear-you-scream/</guid>
      <description>A note if you&amp;rsquo;re leaving a review for any app on the App Store:
 Reviews are very helpful for letting the world know what you think of an app. Additionally, the more reviews an app gets, the higher it ranks when someone searches the App Store, which improves its visibility and &amp;ldquo;discoverability&amp;rdquo;. Developers of the app can&amp;rsquo;t reply to your reviews. So, if your review contains some kind of support request (&amp;ldquo;the app crashes when I do X&amp;rdquo;), the developer can&amp;rsquo;t get in touch with you to help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, Per.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/09/hello-per/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2015/02/09/hello-per/</guid>
      <description>Pop quiz, hotshot: you&amp;rsquo;re in produce section at the supermarket, and you need carrots for tonight&amp;rsquo;s dinner.
Raw carrots are $1.09 per pound. Washed baby carrots are $1.99 for 907 grams.
What do you do?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
 Per was created to answer exactly that question. It was inspired by my wife, who literally turned to me at the grocery store and said,
 &amp;ldquo;You should write an app that tells me which of these options is a better deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honeyjar v1.1 released</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/10/09/honeyjar-v11-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/10/09/honeyjar-v11-released/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve just released v1.1 of HoneyJar, a free update now available on the App Store.
This version adds support for iOS 8 and fixes a display bug on the iPhones 6, along with a smattering of other small bug fixes and performance enhancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, HoneyJar.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/09/04/hello-honeyjar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/09/04/hello-honeyjar/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to announce that HoneyJar, our first app for iPhone and iPod touch, has been released for sale.

You give every dollar you spend a job, whether you realize it or not.
In fact—if you want to take it to the extreme—you can argue that every dollar that isn&amp;rsquo;t working for you, is working against you. It&amp;rsquo;s keeping you from an early retirement. It&amp;rsquo;s keeping you from financial independence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World.</title>
      <link>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/08/25/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://droppedbits.com/news/2014/08/25/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to announce that—after what feels like an eternity—our first app for iPhone, HoneyJar, was submitted on Sunday for approval to the App Store team.
This marks a pretty big milestone, obviously. Dropped Bits incorporated almost three years ago, so it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time coming, too. And it&amp;rsquo;s been an interesting road so far, full of inspiration, hard decisions, learning, sacrifice, and happy little victories.
Turns out, going from idea to shipping your Minimum Viable Product isn&amp;rsquo;t as simple as you&amp;rsquo;d think—especially when your organization is having an identity crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
